Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
H0
band
nain
bend
music
Music
Hey, can I take a bath?
I just need to do some writing.
Magitako.
Gaston Gourmet, you're going to put in a magic octopus?
I just put in quite a few snacks this morning.
I thought it would be convenient.
My bento has Chinese food in it.
Isn't it a little brown?
It's a little brown, isn't it?
This bed is a little brown.
What about me?
But wait a minute.
Here's some color.
And here are some tomatoes.
I grew these tomatoes with my incompetence.
I'm also a yakitori chef.
Ah!
LOL!
What's that supposed to appeal to? LOL!
They're both losing.
Appeal.
But they're definitely going at it.
What shall we do?
I'm going to make a clock that eats both of them.
Oh, lol!
LOL!
Sorry about the tomatoes.
Uma!